(Bernadette:)Did you...
A plaque?
(Sheldon:)Nobody wants to see this.
Well, change "plaque"
to "mixed-race couple"
(Leonard:)and you are my grandma.
I can't take this anymore.
(Sheldon:)Bert. Bert.
Bert!
(Bert:)Come in.
(Sheldon:)All right, let's do this...
(Sheldon:)Bert?
(Sheldon:)We need to talk.
(Penny:)What happened to you?
(Sheldon:)Rock, rock, water fountain.
(Sheldon:)I am not proud of this.
(Sheldon:)But I have been envious
of your recent success.
(Bert:)Wow, I won the MacArthur Grant,
(Bert:)everyone's jealous of me.
(Bert:)Once I get Lasik, I'll be
out of things to wish for.
(Sheldon:)I was hoping by admitting
my weakness to you,
(Sheldon:)I'd somehow be unburdened.
(Bert:)Is it working?
No.
(Sheldon:)Now that you know my weakness,
(Sheldon:)I hate you more than ever.
(Bert:)Well, you know, we're
both pretty smart.